Hritthik Bose

Silvassa | contact@hritthik.com | 8003031332 | linkedin.com/in/hritthikb/

About Me

Cloud Engineer at Insight Enterprises with 3+ years of experience specializing in application development and internal GenAI product solutions. Full-stack developer with expertise in C#, .NET 8, Blazor, Microsoft Fluent UI, and advanced CSS customization.

Skills

Programming Languages: C#, Python, JavaScript, C++

Frameworks & Libraries: Blazor Server, .NET, React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, FluentUI

Cloud Platforms: Microsoft Azure, AWS, GCP

Databases: SQL, CosmosDB

AI & ML: Semantic Kernel, Azure OpenAI, RAG Implementation Tools & Methodologies: Git, Agile - Jira, CI/CD - Github Actions

Experience

Insight Enterprises – Cloud Engineer, Gen AI Developer

Apr 2023 - Present

- Addressed complexities of information retrieval from extensive SharePoint repositories, developing efficient data ingestion pipelines for fetching, chunking, and indexing data into Azure Search
- Spearheaded the implementation of a RAG-based enterprise application, leveraging Semantic Kernel, C# .NET 8 Blazor, and Microsoft Fluent UI to create a robust and scalable solution
- Orchestrated multi-LLM support and designed an intuitive chatbot interface, streamlining user experience and enhancing data accessibility
- Optimized application performance by tackling technical challenges, resolving performance bottlenecks, and making key architectural decisions

Technologies: C# .NET 8 Blazor, Microsoft Fluent UI, Semantic Kernel, Azure OpenAI Studio, Azure Search

Hanu Softwares (acquired by Insight) - Product Development, Hybrid Cloud

Jul 2022 - Mar 2023

• Contributed to product development and hybrid cloud deployments

Technologies: Node.js, React, Azure, AWS, Azure SQL Elastic Pool

High Radius – Tech Consulting Intern

Aug 2021 – Oct 2021

- Delivered product to client, EIPP product Functional Consulting role
- Gathered requirements, took feedback, configured products, made action plans, and ensured shipping pipeline Technologies: *Jira, Agile, Git, Putty*

High Radius – Full Stack Dev Intern

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

- Worked on EIPP development team
- Built RandomForest model to predict customer payment behavior
- Worked on the front end using React.js and backend using Java J2EE

Technologies: React, Java, Postman, Git, Putty, SQL, Python, Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn

Certifications

Azure: AZ-204, AZ-900, DP-900, AI-900 | AWS: CLF-C02, GCP: ACE | GitHub: Foundations

Education

KIIT University – B. Tech in Information Technology, 8.75gpa

2018-22